椅子摆在那边
Set them up over here.
十二步骤和十二条例
十二条例
众议院第684议案
法案
安德伍德
马修斯
副总统马修斯
Vice President Matthews.
-鲍勃  -副总统先生
- Bob. - Mr. Vice President.
安德伍德
乌麦克
吉布森
马修斯
-副总统先生  -弗兰克
- Mr. Vice President. - Frank.
先生  请站在姓名标识处
Sir, I'm gonna need you to stand on your mark.
我站这儿就好了
I'm fine right here.
各位  还有两分钟
Two minutes, people.
他们把我从车里拖出来
So they pull me from the car.
俩腿都断了  颅骨撞裂了
Both legs broken, fractured skull,
肺也刺穿了
punctured lung.
心脏停止跳动  整整两分钟
My heart stops. Two full minutes.
医生人工起搏  没反应
They're pumping my chest. Nothing.
又用了除纤颤器   嘭
They grab the defibrillators. Pachoom!
还是没反应
Nothing.
到第三次  心脏才开始跳动
Third time, the pistons start firing.
医生们说我能活下来是个奇迹
Doctors tell me it's a miracle I'm alive.
但要知道  这是上帝敲的警钟
But, seriously, you talk about a wake-up call from God.
死里逃生这种事不会有第二次
You don't get to come back from the dead twice.
美利坚合众国总统
The President of the United States.
早上好
Good morning.
由我签署并于今天生效的
"The education reform and achievement act
《教育改革和成就法案》
that I sign into law today
与全国的孩子及家长息息相关
will affect every child and parent in the United States,
它将改善未来数十年的教学水平
will ensure a better educated workforce for decades to come,
巩固并强化美国
and will reinforce America's
作为教育强国的领先地位
preeminence as an intellectual superpower.
在此我要特别感谢一个人
And I'd like to thank one man in particular
他富有远见卓识
who never lost sight of the larger mission,
并带领完成了这部法案
who spearheaded this bill from the beginning,
他就是弗兰克・安德伍德议员
and that's congressman Frank Underwood."
各位贵宾  东厅备有点心  请随我们来
Invited guests, please join us in the east room for refreshments.
媒体朋友们
Media, we will
我们马上将在简报室集中开会
convene immediately in the briefing room for our conference.
谢谢你  琳达  法案能够顺利通过
Linda, thank you so much for all the help you gave us
你功不可没啊
in getting this bill passed.
不  谢谢你  弗兰克
No, thank you, Frank.
这完全是你的心血
This was your baby from the beginning.
幸好你能坚持己见  弗兰克
I appreciate you standing your ground on this one,  Frank.
我还知道有错就该承认
I'm smart enough to admit when I was wrong.
我刚才还跟弗兰克说该每周碰次面
I was just telling Frank we should set up a weekly
让他向我们汇报众议院那边的动态
so he can keep us up to date on what's going on in the house.
听上去是个好主意
That sounds like a great idea.
恭喜  先生
Congratulations, sir.
加勒特  我们能谈一下吗
Garrett, I was wondering if we could talk for a few minutes.
几周前我对你提起的那件事
That thing I mentioned a couple of weeks ago
有关就业税收抵免
about the jobs tax credit...
我想了很多  吉姆
I've been giving it a lot of thought, Jim,
觉得这主意不错
and I think it's a good idea.
不介意的话我想去翻翻备忘录
But I'd like to look over my notes first, if you don't mind,
这样就能和你自如探讨了
so I can talk about it intelligently with you.
先生  首相来电
Sir, you have your call with the Prime Minister.
大忙人
Busy man.
没错
Yes, he is.
弗兰克  听说你打算
Frank, I hear that you are heading up
去我家乡参与一场补选
the special election in my home state.
-彼得・罗素  -在正式声明前
- Peter Russo. - We're trying to keep that
我们打算低调行事
under the radar until he officially announces.
事实上  在那之前
In fact, we're not even working
我们都不在我办公室办公
out of my office until that happens.
-那在哪呢  -我家地下室
- Where are you working from? - The basement of my house.
民主党全国委员会
Any reason why the D.N.C.
怎么不就候选人征询我呢
didn't ask my advice on the candidate?
我以为他们或琳达获得了你的首肯
Well, I thought they passed it by you, or Linda did.
-但他们没有  -这真是无法接受
- Nobody did. - Well, that is unacceptable.
而且我对罗素持怀疑态度
And I have major doubts about Russo.
-经验不足吗  -对  他立足于城市
- His inexperience? - Yes, and he's urban-based.
不知道他能不能和农村选民打交道
I don't know if he'll connect with rural voters.
老实说  这也是我的顾虑之一
Look, frankly, that's one of my concerns as well.
我们正在想办法
We're working on that.
但如果你能跟他一起做竞选宣传
But if you were to come out and stump with him,
那对他将极为有利
that would go a long way to convince...
弗兰克  我不能为我不信任的人作宣传
Frank, I can't stump for somebody I don't believe in.
现在还早  希望你别急着下定论
It's early days yet. I'd ask you to keep an open mind.
如果想让我
And let me know if you want me
安排你们见面尽管说
to set up a meeting between the two of you,
因为你的支持  先生
because, sir, an endorsement from you
对他是莫大的帮助
would be a big coup for him.
见到你真好  副总统先生
It's good to see you, Mr. Vice President.
弗兰克
Frank.
安德伍德议员
Congressman Underwood?
巴恩斯小姐  我怎么记得
Miss Barnes, I was under the impression
你不想来做白宫记者
you didn't wanna cover the White House.
头条网昨天才拿到许可
Slugline just got access yesterday.
-我听说了  -我离开《先驱报》
- I know. - I left the Herald
正是因为不愿来白宫
because I didn't wanna cover the White House,
现在我还是来了
and now here I am.
许可和镣铐还是有点区别的
Access isn't the same as a ball and chain.
我只有在签法案时才能见到你咯
Am I only gonna see you at bill signings now?
我已经三周没有你的消息了
I haven't heard from you in three weeks.
没有安全感很无聊
Insecurity bores me.
居高临下也让我觉得无聊
I feel the same way about condescension.
今晚你家见
Your place, this evening,
来之前我会给你短信
and I'll text you when I'm about to arrive.
要是我到时候在忙呢
What if I'm busy?
你只是怕再被放鸽子
You're just afraid I'm gonna stand you up again.
我只想确定这值得我等
I just wanna make sure it's worth my while.
会值得的
It'll be worth your while.
这是对上次的补偿
This'll make up for last time.
历史的见证物
It's a piece of history.
从总统手里传到了你这儿
From the President's hand to yours.
你相信他们刚刚说的上帝什么的吗
You believe in all that higher-power stuff they talk about in the room?
我相信总有事情是我们无法掌控的
I believe there are things beyond our control.
至于谁掌控着这些事  我不知道
Who or what's controlling them... that I don't know.
我不相信上帝
I don't believe in God.
天堂  地狱  什么都不信
Heaven, hell. None of it.
-天主教会学校上多了  -或许吧
- Too much catholic school? - Maybe.
彼得  我不是说你非得信上帝
I'm not saying you have to believe in God, Peter,
或者其他任何事
or anything, for that matter.
但也别急着否定一切
But you shouldn't rule anything out.
我要走了
I should go.
帐记在竞选经费上
It's on the campaign.
道格・斯坦普  收
我还需要钱  别塞嘴里
民调数据显示81%可能投票的选民
Our crosstabs show 81% of likely voters
会考虑投给戒酒的候选人
are willing to consider a recovering alcoholic.
如果换成可卡因的话这个数字会下降
Now, those numbers dip a little when you introduce cocaine,
但不会下降很多
but not by much.
兰迪
Randy?
有风险  不过轰动是肯定的
It's a risk, but it'll make waves.
免费得到主流媒体的关注和报道
Free coverage across the board.
竞选主题得是救赎
The narrative has to be redemption.
凤凰从灰烬中涅
A Phoenix from the ashes.
就别提灰烬了
Well, let's not focus on the ashes.
别让大家觉得彼得过去一团乱
We don't want people to think Peter was a disaster.
不  我们侧重积极的一面
No, no. We focus on the positive.
"崭新"或"干净"的开始
A "Fresh start" And a "Clean start"
焦点小组对这两个词都很喜欢
both did well in focus groups.
"干净的开始"听着像是洗白的
"Clean start" sounds too much like "Clean slate."
-我喜欢"崭新的开始"  -我也是
- I like "Fresh start." - Yeah, I do too.
筹款怎么样了
How we doing on the fund-raising?
酗酒史会使他失去一些州内捐款
The alcoholic thing will turn off some of the in-state donors,
但这不是大型选举
but it's an off-year election.
我们可以去纽约和加州找找老金主
We can hit up the usual suspects in New York and California.
沃尔特  我们有多少弱点
Walter, how vulnerable are we?
这还难说
I'm not prepared to answer that question.
彼得还没向我忏悔呢
Peter and I have yet to perform the holy sacrament of confession.
关闭造船厂一事我们也得有所表示
We still need to address the shipyard closing too.
这方面克莱尔在处理
Claire's helping us with that.
我们在推动一项
We are pushing a bill
《特拉华河流域法案》
called the Delaware river watershed Act,
预计将在三年内
and I think it's going to bring about
为彼得的选区带来约五千个岗位
5,000 jobs into Peter's district over the next three years.
我们已经完成了一份草案
We have a draft of the bill completed.
彼得正在找法案的连署者
Peter's in the process of securing cosponsors.
对了  你都问过谁了
And who have you called, by the way?
我发了几份邮件
I have some e-mails out,
大多数想先看看法案
but most of them wanna see a bill first.
船厂那边你约过谁见面了吗
Have you set up a meeting with the shipbuilders yet?
我不认为他们会支持我
I don't think they're gonna back me.
法案就是为了他们啊  彼得
That's the entire point of the bill, Peter.
如果我去跟他们说
Well, if I go to them and I say,
你们有些人可能会重新找到工作
"Hey, some of you maybe will get your jobs back,
不过不是明天  而是三年后
"Not tomorrow, but three years from now,
大多数还得继续失业在家
and most of you won't be getting your jobs back anyway... "
好吧  先找联署人  这事暂且放一边
All right, let's put a pin in this until we get more sponsors.
我要回趟办公室  晚点再过来
I have to go to the office. I'll catch you all later.
好了  说一下竞选方案吧
Okay, let's move on to our field plan.
要逐个区讨论...
I want to go through the regions one by one...
弗兰西斯
Francis.
我们在这个法案上花了六周时间
We spent six weeks on that bill.
不会有问题  他会想明白的
It'll be fine. He'll come around.
那晚上见
I'll see you later tonight?
我有约了
I have an appointment.
那我明天早上才能见到你了
So I won't see you until morning.
我会在你起床前回来
I'll be back before you get up.
感谢你今天能抽出时间过来  先生
I appreciate your taking the time today, sir.
经济研究小组起草的
Did you get that tax credit memo
税收抵免备忘录你拿到了吗
the economic research team put together?
你叫我来不是为了讨论备忘录吧
You didn't ask me here to talk about memos.
有话直说吧  琳达
I know small talk when I hear it, Linda.
总统希望你
The President has asked
不要过分插手宾州的事务
that you take a step back from Pennsylvania.
你最近经常去那儿
You've been taking a lot of trips there,
与立法者会面...
meeting with legislators...
那是我的家乡  而且正面临着就业危机
It's my home state. There's a jobs crisis.
我们不能偏帮单个州
We can't afford to play favorites.
我们的方针是五十个州  一套解决方案
The message is 50 states, one solution;
而不是一个州  五十套方案
not one state, 50 solutions.
我并没指望能参与每一项政策和决策的制定
I never expected to be involved in every policy or decision,
但我现在是什么事都被蒙在鼓里
but I have been completely cut out of everything.
我们很重视你的意见  副总统先生
We value your input, Mr. Vice President,
但现在我们不能...
but right now, we can't...
别一副高高在上的口气  琳达
Don't condescend, Linda.
甚至都没人问我希望由谁来接替州长一职
No one even asked me who I thought should fill my seat.
为什么这事是弗兰克・安德伍德牵头而不是我
Why is Frank Underwood leading the charge on that, not me?
那是民主党全国委员会的决定
That is a D.N.C. issue.
我们不会插手  你也一样
We are staying out of it and so should you.
那我就只能负责剪彩和出席葬礼吗
And so I'm supposed to just cut ribbons and go to funerals?
你应该清楚你的职责范围
You knew what you signed up for.
谢谢你  副总统先生
Thank you, Mr. Vice President.
我没拿到我的钢笔
I didn't get my pen.
-你的钢笔  -签署法案的笔
- Your pen? - From the bill signing.
我们会想办法解决的
Oh, we'll see what we can do about that.
我看到你的保镖了
I can see your security guy.
密查姆吗
Meechum?
他可真帅
He's cute.
他不会喜欢你的
He'd never go for you.
为什么
Why not?
你令他生畏
You're too intimidating.
可他有枪啊
He's the one with the gun.
但你有议员
But you're the one with the congressman.
我们做完再谈
We'll talk after.
我们谈完再做
We'll talk before.
彼得・罗素
Peter Russo.
宾州第一选区的议员
Pennsylvania's first district.
他会竞选州长
He's gonna run for governor.
接替马修斯的职位
Fill Matthews' seat.
这会是一篇独家专访
It's an exclusive profile.
但对象是个无名小卒
With someone no one's ever heard of.
报道角度呢
What's the angle?
酗酒  吸毒
Alcohol, drugs.
他是个出身贫寒的野孩子
He's a kid from the streets.
我希望专访能在他宣布参选后马上发布
I want the profile to come out as soon as he announces,
并且向着他说话
and I'd like it to be kind.
我不写吹捧报道
I don't write puff pieces.
那就找别人写
Then get someone else to write it.
我以为你有料给我
I thought you had something for me.
人们很容易就会猜到我是你的消息来源
It's too easy for people to link me as your source.
那就危险了
It's dangerous.
把头条让给别人  我得不到好处啊
I don't benefit from handing out headlines to other people.
别低估了慷慨的力量  佐伊
Generosity is its own form of power, Zoe.
第六步
Step six.
第七步
Step seven.
你总是大晚上戴墨镜吗
You always wear sunglasses at night?
你怎么找到我的
How did you find me?
我猜你肯定是公务员
I figured you had to be in government.
就在网上搜索  终于找到你的照片
I kept googling till I found your picture.
这招没用的
This won't work, what you're doing.
那次是一锤子买卖
It was a one-time deal.
你不能一直要挟我
You don't get to keep coming back for more.
我会去报警
I'll go to the police.
他们只会当面嘲笑你  瞧你这样子
They'll laugh in your face. Look at you.
如果警察不信我
If the police won't listen to me,
我就爆料给电视台
I'll call TV stations.
我知道你们是谁
I know the names...
道格拉斯・斯坦普  彼得・罗素
Douglas Stamper, Peter Russo,
弗兰克・安德伍德
Frank Underwood.
你现在走的是条危险的路
You are walking down a road you do not want to walk down.
求你了  我不会说出去的
Please, I won't call anyone.
但我需要你的帮助
But I need your help.
我无处可去  没有人可以联系
I don't have anywhere to go. I don't have anyone I can call.
我不再想做我现在做的一些事了
I've had to do things. And I don't wanna do it anymore.
现在我身上就这么多
That's all I've got right now.
找个住处  告诉我地址
Find a place to stay and let me know where you are.
我会再想办法的
I'll figure something out.
饿吗
You hungry?
你叫什么名字
What's your name?
蓝宝石
Sapphire.
不是这个名字  本名
No. What's your name?
瑞秋
Rachel.
你前妻做过什么不体面的事吗
Your ex-wife... anything uncouth?
什么意思
How do you mean?
性虐待  群交  掺尿纵欲
Bondage, orgies, water sports?
-没有  绝对没有  -吸食毒品吗
- No. Definitely not. - Narcotics?
-她不好这口  -大麻都不来点
- She wasn't into that. - Not even a little ganga?
好吧  心情低落时抽过
Okay. Once in a blue moon.
跟孩子一起抽过吗
Ever with your children?
-天呐  怎么可能  -在孩子面前抽过吗
- God, no! - Ever in front of them?
听着  我不是个绝世好爸
Look, I'm not the world's best dad,
但我绝不会做那种事
but I would never do that.
好的  我们来谈谈招妓问题吧
Fine. Let's move on to prostitution.
还要问多久
How long is this gonna take?
直到我完全了解你为止
Until there's nothing I don't know about you.
我全都写下来了
I wrote all this down.
我做这行很久了  议员先生
I've been doing this a long time, congressman.
我知道什么时候才算完
I know when I've scraped all the shit off the shoe.
招妓问题
Prostitution.
离婚后  我去了趟泰国旅行
After my divorce, I took a trip to Thailand.
大概待了两周
It was about two weeks.
找了多少女人
How many women?
10人  15人
Ten. Fifteen.
我不确定  记忆有些模糊了
I... I don't know. It was a bit of a blur.
沾毒品了没
There were drugs?
沾了
Uh, yes.
鸦片  安非他明[兴奋剂]
Opium, speed,
海洛因都用了
some smack.
-吸粉还是注射  -都来
- Powder or needles? - Both.
她们知道你是谁吗
Would any of these women know who you are?
没有  她们都不说英语
No. None of them spoke English.
我也从未提过自己是议员
And I never mentioned I was a congressman.
你在国内注射过海洛因吗
Have you mainlined heroin back here in the States?
-就一次  -胳膊上有疤痕吗
- Just once. - Any scars on your arm?
没有  我主要吸食可卡因
No. I was mainly into cocaine.
在特区招妓呢
What about prostitutes here in D.C.?
多久一次
How often?
-我有时会乱搞  行了吧  -请说详细点
- I fucked around a bit, okay? - Details, please.
这种事让你很来劲吗
Do you get off on this or something?
医生托着你的蛋让你咳嗽时
Does a doctor enjoy it when he cups your balls
他享不享受呢
and asks you to cough?
你想知道我来过几次高潮吗
You wanna know how many times I came?
我根本不在乎你能否当选
I honestly don't care whether you win.
但你想当选  就得跟我合作
But if you do, work with me.
你在特区多久招一回妓
How often did you solicit prostitutes in D.C.?
两到三个月一次
Once every two or three months.
有时频繁些  有时会少些
Sometimes more frequently, sometimes less.
你有理由相信她们中有人未成年吗
Do you have reason to believe any of them were underage?
天呐  没有  大多是高端妓女
Jesus! No. Look, they were mostly high-end.
那不代表她们都到18岁了
That doesn't mean they were 18.
我得休息一下
I need a fucking break!
怎么了
What's going on?
他道行太浅  弗兰克
He's an amateur, Frank.
如果我不到一小时就激怒了他
If I can get under his skin in less than an hour,
面对媒体攻击他能撑多久呢
how do you think he'll hold up under the press?
会被人当活靶子打
It'll be a Turkey shoot.
知道了  我会跟他谈的
All right. I'll speak to him.
弗兰克  这...不行
Frank, it's just... it's not gonna work.
我会被折磨死的
I'm gonna get crucified.
没事的  我们有最好的团队帮你
You'll be fine. We've got a crack team behind you.
不是说团队好就行了
It doesn't matter how good the team is.
像我这样的过去  算了吧
I mean with my past? Come on.
我一开始就把方案告诉你了
From the very beginning, I said this was the plan.
-你也同意的  -当时我没考虑清楚
- You agreed to it. - I didn't think it through.
我们必须直面这些问题
We have to tackle this head-on,
否则共和党就真要整死你了
or the G.O.P. will crucify you.
我们需要借力打力
We have to steal their ammunition from them.
坦诚是你最佳防御也是最佳攻击
Honesty is your best defense and offense.
要上镜头说这些话的人是我
I'm the one that has to get in front of these cameras and say this shit.
他们又不用说  是我
They don't have to say it. I do.
-彼得...  -我想成为州长  真的
- Peter... - I wanna be governor. I do.
但不能以这种方式  我做不来
But not this way. I just can't do it.
如果你现在没打退堂鼓
If you weren't unsure now,
那才叫有毛病呢
there'd be something wrong with you.
这是预料之中
I expected this.
我们要你做的事并不容易
Not easy... what we're asking you to do.
犹豫是正常的
It's okay to vacillate a little.
我不是想妨碍你们
I'm not trying to throw a wrench in the works.
这我知道  跟你说
I know you're not. I'll tell you what.
你今天先回去吧
You take the rest of the day off.
回你办公室去
You go back to your office,
赶一下落下的工作
you catch up with whatever you have to catch up on,
回去睡个好觉  明天开个会
you get a good night's sleep, you go to a meeting tomorrow,
然后再过来  我们把整件事好好谈谈
and then you come here and we'll talk the whole thing through.
这你总能办到吧
Can you give me at least that?
好的  没问题  弗兰克
Yeah. Okay, Frank.
很好
Good.
那些小折纸是怎么回事
What's going on with all the little sculptures?
我在餐桌上看到一朵花
I found a flower on the dining room table
几天前床头柜上还有只鸟
and a bird on the nightstand a few days ago.
那是天鹅
It's a swan.
都是你做的
You made them?
是的
Yes.
新爱好吗
A new hobby?
不是
No.
只是心血来潮而已
It's an interest.
能说说我留意到的另一件事吗
May I bring up something else I've noticed?
什么事
What's that?
你...
You...
站在冰箱前面
standing in front of the refrigerator.
你为什么一直都没有跟我谈
Is there a reason you haven't talked to me about it?
因我觉得没必要
I haven't felt the need to.
严重吗
Is it bad?
不是什么好事
It's not pleasant.
不过  并不严重
But, no, it's not bad.
我能做什么吗
What can I do?
不用
Nothing.
如果有需要我会告诉你的
If there was something, I'd ask.
我打电话给你  你觉得奇怪吗
Did you think it was weird that I called you?
简直太奇怪了
Totally weird.
不过我那时也正好想打给你
Except for the fact that I was planning on calling you.
是吗  为什么
Really? Why?
我在《先驱报》时对你态度很不好
I was a real grade-A bitch to you at the Herald,
在白宫见到你时  我差点想道歉了
and I almost apologized when I saw you at the White House,
但我退缩了
but I chickened out.
反正我也喝高了  对不起
So, anyway, I am drunk enough, and I am sorry.
你为什么打电话给我呢
Why did you call me?
我只是想知道
I was just wondering how
咱们老地方现在怎么样了
things were going at the old stomping ground.
-你的酒  -谢谢
- Here you go. - Thank you.
汤姆离开后就不一样了
It's just not the same since tom left.
我倒不怪你那么做
And I don't blame you for doing what you did.
可新来的这家伙
But this new guy?
在网版《娱乐周刊》干了六年
Six years running E.W. Online
可不是做总编的材料
does not a managing editor make.
你想过来我们这儿工作吗
Would you ever wanna come work with us?
那可是个大事啊
I mean, it'd be a huge fucking deal.
《先驱报》的首席政治记者
Chief political correspondent of the Herald
跳槽到头条网
moves to Slugline?
是卡莉・希斯让你来劝我的吗
Did carly heath put you up to this?
不  跟她没关系
No. Not at all.
不过如果你想  我可以跟她谈谈
But if you want, I can talk to her.
你觉得她会同意吗
You think she would go for it?
老实说  我也不知道
Honestly, I don't know.
她对正统比较不屑一顾
She's got this sort of anti-establishment "fuck you" attitude.
常规的新闻她不感兴趣
Conventional news bores her.
但你要是有猛料...
But if you had something gritty to show...
要是你有兴趣  我倒是有料
I've got a story if you want it.
而且是惊天猛料
It's pretty fucking great.
你要把新闻让我
You would give away a story?
如果你没兴趣就算了
If you're not interested...
不  我感兴趣
no, I'm interested.
如果我有点像宿醉未醒  是因为事实如此
If I seem a little hung over, it is because I am.
其实还不止有点
A lot hung over, actually.
天呐  我都戒了几个月了
God, I almost had a couple of months,
然后昨天晚上  我...
and then last night, I...
其实我也不太记得了
Well, I don't remember much, so...
无论如何  我回来了
But anyway, here I am.
坚持来
Keep coming back.
努力就会有回报
It works if you work it.
谢谢你的分享  戴安
Thank you for sharing, Diane.
我是道格  我是个酒鬼
I'm Doug, and I'm an alcoholic.
道格  你好
Hi, Doug.
我工作的一部分就是数数
One of the things I do for a living is count.
我数选票
I count votes.
同意票  反对票  中立票  弃权票
Yeas, nays, neutrals, abstaining.
而且我很熟练
And I'm good at it.
不过对我最重要的数字跟工作无关
But the most important count I do has nothing to do with work.
而是从1999年4月4日至今的天数
It's the number of days since April 4, 1999.
截止今早  一共有5185天
As of this morning, that's 5,185.
数字越大  我越感到害怕
The bigger that number gets, the more it frightens me,
因为我知道一杯酒就能让数字清零
because I know all it takes is one drink to go back to zero.
很多人认为恐惧是弱点
Most people see fear as a weakness.
有时是的
It can be.
有时由于工作的关系  我要让他人生惧
Sometimes for my job, I have to put fear in other people.
我知道那样不对
I know that's not right.
但如果按第四步说的那样  实话实说
But if I'm honest, like the fourth step asks us to be,
互诫会的"十二步骤"  第四步: 做一次彻底勇敢的自我道德反省
我必须残忍  因为我不能失败
I have to be ruthless, because failure is not an option.
戒酒也是如此
The same goes for my sobriety.
我要对自己残忍
I have to be ruthless with myself.
我得利用恐惧
I have to use my fear.
它让我变得坚强
It makes me stronger.
就像在座各位  我无法改变本性
Like everyone in this room, I can't control who I am.
但我能控制那个零
But I can control the zero.
让那个零去死吧
Fuck the zero.
多谢分享
Thanks for sharing.
努力就会有回报
It works if you work it.
接下来谁想分享
Who would like to share next?
-他参加互诫会了吗  -是的
- Was he at the meeting? - He was.
之后我想找他
I tried to find him afterwards,
但我追上去时他已经没影了
but he was gone before I could catch up with him.
-他说什么了吗  -没有
- Did he say anything? - No.
他从不分享  满腹心事的样子
He never shares. He looked preoccupied.
-他今天会去众议院吗  -我不清楚
- You think he'll show up at the house today? - I have no idea.
他不接我的电话
He's not answering my calls.
也不接我的  还有别的事吗
Mine neither. Anything else I need to know?
我听见沉默了  我可不喜欢那声音
I hear silence. I don't like that sound.
出了些事情  我在处理
Something came up. I'm handling it.
-严重吗  -严重但能解决
- Something serious? - Serious but solvable.
我需要知道更多吗
Do I wanna know more?
不用  我们会没事的
I don't think you do. We'll be okay.
我可能会要南茜帮忙  但愿用不着
I might have to involve Nancy. I'm hoping I won't have to.
即使别无他法  也不会让她知道什么不利的事
But if I do, she'll have no knowledge of anything damaging.
好吧  你自己想好就行
All right. Use your best judgment.
当然  先生
Of course, sir.
我得挂了
I've gotta go.
盖拉格小姐
Miss Gallagher?
议员有话想和你说
Can the congressman have a moment?
事情  很复杂
Things are... they're complicated.
我知道  但他真的需要你
I realize that, but he truly needs you.
我不知道能和他说什么
I don't know what I could say to him.
我想你的出现就能让他好很多
I think just showing up would do him a world of good.
我今天很忙  议长的日程表很满
Today is tough. The speaker has a full schedule...
我已经和鲍勃谈过了
Look, I already spoke to Bob,
他同意让你今天休假
and he said he'd be fine if you took the rest of the day off.
事实上  如果你想休半年
In fact, he said he'd be fine if you wanted to take
-他也同意  -什么
- the next six months off. - What?
我想让你做副竞选经理
I want you to be deputy campaign manager.
在纳什・埃伦斯手下干
You work under Nash Aarons.
不  我给彼得当了好几年的拐杖
No. I spent years being Peter's crutch.
如果你只是想让我去...
If you just want me there...
我们当然想让你去帮忙  但不是做拐杖
Well, of course we want you there to help, but not as a crutch.
彼得是个有才华又有潜力的年轻人
Peter is a talented young man with a lot of potential.
这他知道  但他需要我之外的人的认同
He knows this, but he needs to hear it from someone other than me.
某个他真心在乎的人
Someone he truly cares about.
抱歉  我一下子接受不了
I'm sorry. This is just a lot right now.
你不用马上做决定
Well, you don't have to make a decision now,
但至少和彼得谈谈
but at least talk to Peter.
这总没什么坏处  是吗
I mean, there's no harm in that, now, is there?
一万块
Ten grand.
从你的竞选账户里出
We divert it from your campaign accounts.
-分散款项  做成...  -等等
- We itemize it so it looks like... - Wait.
你要我为这事买单
You want me to pay for this?
去用弗兰克的连任基金
Use Frank's reelection fund.
局长  你筹集到的大部分钱
Commissioner, the majority of the money that you've raised
都来自于我们为你找的资助人
has come from people we've sent your way.
那是因为
And you sent them because
我摆平了罗素的事在先
I sprung your boy Russo in the first place.
我们扯平了  我不欠你的
We're even. I don't owe you shit.
这女孩有麻烦  我们得帮她
There's a girl in trouble. Let's help her out.
-不是我的问题  -这难说
- Not my problem. - It could be.
我们不管她
We put her back on the streets,
她不一定会做出什么事
there's no telling what she could do.
比起一个妓女
I'm a hell of a lot more afraid
我更怕联邦检察官
of the U.S. attorney than I am of some hooker.
这是张廉价的保单
This is a very inexpensive insurance policy.
我已经犯过一次法了  道格
I already broke the law once, Doug.
我绝不会违反竞选法规
There's no fucking way I'm gonna mess with campaign finance regulations.
我不想再听这些屁话了
I don't even wanna be hearing this shit.
前日本大使的葬礼  明早九点半
Funeral for the former ambassador of Japan tomorrow at 9:30,
接下来是美国女童子军
followed by a luncheon for the national board
全国理事会的午餐会
of directors for the girl scouts of America.
-总统先生  -吉姆
- Mr. President. - Jim.
之后是和决赛选手的见面会...
After that, you've got a meet and greet with the finalist...
等会儿再说吧
I'll catch up with you in a minute.
这边走  先生
This way, sir.
你在这儿干什么
What are you doing here?
议员先生让我过来的
The congressman wanted me to come over.
-为什么  -他要我帮你竞选
- Why? - He wants me to work for your campaign.
-做你的副竞选经理  -弗兰克
- Deputy Manager. - Frank!
他说你还有些顾虑
He said you're having some doubts.
我正想告诉他我决定不参选了
I was just about to tell him that I decided not to run.
好吧  如果你已经决定了
Okay. Um, if you've made up your mind,
那我或许该走了
then I should probably get going.
他把整个计划都告诉你了吗
Did he tell you about the whole plan?
要我坦白一切
About coming clean?
对  他说了
Yeah, he did.
我得为凯文和萨拉考虑
I have Kevin and Sarah to think about.
-每个人都有过去  -但不像我这样
- Everyone has a past. - Not like mine.
你不知道我太多事  克里斯蒂娜
You don't know half the things I've done, Christina.
我的孩子识字  他们的朋友识字
My kids read. Their friends read.
我不能冒这个险
I can't take that chance.
如果你不想竞选  那就退出
Look, if you don't wanna run, then you shouldn't.
我想竞选
I do wanna run.
如果我不想就不会走到这一步
I wouldn't have let it go this far if I didn't want it.
那或许这会是件好事...
Then maybe it's a good thing...
直面你的过去  对你的孩子也好
confronting your past, even for your kids.
他们比你想的要坚强得多
They're a lot stronger than you give them credit for.
如果安德伍德和民主党全国委员会
Look, if Underwood, if the D.N.C.,
他们都认为你能行  那么...
if they all think you can do it, then...
我不在乎他们怎么想  我在乎你怎么想
I don't care what they think. I care what you think.
我认为你会很棒的
I think you'd be great.
-她真想来  -反正我是这么觉得
- So, she really wants this? - That's the impression I got.
她脾气怎么样  我可不想招个耍大牌的来
What about ego? I don't need to be dealing with a diva.
她不是那样的  她是个有15年经验的
She's not a diva, she's an award-winning journalist
获过奖的记者
with 15 years' experience.
是你跟我说她待你很糟
You told me she treated you like shit.
我们之间是有过不快
There was some friction.
那你现在为什么替她说话
So why are you going to bat for her?
难道你不想和最优秀的人一起工作吗
Don't we want to work with the best people?
再说  这对网站也很有利
Plus, it'd be big for the site.
《先驱报》的资深政治记者
The Herald's senior political writer?
话是没错  但她太保守了
Sure, but she's so old guard.
什么都照规矩做
Everything's by the book.
这可没什么意思
There's no bite to it.
她跟我说了她正在做的一篇专访
She told me about a profile she's working on.
-很有意思呢  -关于什么的
- It's got serious bite. - What is it?
让她自己告诉你  你应该跟她谈谈
She can tell you herself. You should talk to her.
这是我的条件
Here's the deal.
不要牵涉到我的孩子
My children stay out of the limelight.
不让他们上镜  或面对媒体
No photo ops, no press.
这是当然
We wouldn't dream of it.
那好
Okay.
我们干吧
Let's do this.
汽车旅馆
坐下吧
Sit down.
-你是哪里人  -林奇堡城外
- Where you from? - Outside of Lynchburg.
-弗吉尼亚州的  -对
- Virginia? - Yeah.
-你父母还住那儿吗  -我不能去找他们
- Are your parents still living there? - No. I can't.
如果我给你找个地方住
If I find a place for you to stay for a while,
你能乖乖的吗
can I count on you to be smart?
-什么样的地方  -很不错的地方
- What kind of place? - A nice place.
安全的地方  让我们有时间想出长久之计
A safe place until we can figure out something permanent.
但我需要知道你不会再做这种事了
But I need to know that you won't pull anything like this again.
向我保证
Promise me.
我保证
I promise.
看着我的眼睛说
Look at me when you say it.
我向你保证
I promise you.
钱还够花吗
How you doing on money?
不够明天花的
I don't have enough for tomorrow.
你干什么
What are you doing?
我以为你要我...
I thought you wanted me to...
你说过不再干了
You said you were done with that.
我会联系你的
I'll be in touch.
性行为: 男性性伙伴: 无; 女性性伙伴: 多个
如果只承认其中一部分事
If you own up to some of the shenanigans,
把其他的掩盖起来  或许还有机会
sweep the rest under the rug, you might have a shot.
得掩盖多少
How much do we have to sweep under?
性经历  招妓  非传统性行为
这孩子隐藏踪迹倒是有一套
Well, the kid had a talent for covering his tracks.
我把他该承认的东西都标出来了
I've highlighted all the items I think he should admit to.
吸毒: 从未吸食海洛因; 曾吸食可卡因; 酗酒
其他的就别提了
The rest I wouldn't mention.
不能说的还挺多
It's a lot not to talk about.
-我需要你帮忙  -现在吗
- I need your help with something. - Right now?
-对  -重要吗
- Yes. - Is it important?
你之前说我这周末可以早点下班
Because you told me I could leave early this weekend
去弗吉尼亚看望我女儿
to go visit my daughter down in Virginia.
你家里有客房吧
You have a guest room in your house, right?
有  原来是玛丽的房间
Well, it's Mary's old room, but, yes.
我想让一个年轻女人去你那儿住一段时间
I need you to put someone up for a while. A young woman.
-什么  谁  -她叫瑞秋
- What? Who? - Her name is Rachel.
只能告诉你这些
I can't tell you anymore than that.
我不明白  你为什么
I don't understand. Why do you need...
别问了  南茜  我需要你帮我
No questions, Nancy. I just need you to do this for me.
如果不重要我就不会开口了
I wouldn't be asking if it weren't serious.
要住多长时间
Put up for how long?
不知道  可能得有一段时间
I don't know. It could be a while.
你让一个陌生人去我家住
I'm supposed to put up a complete stranger
还不许我提问吗
and not ask any questions?
南茜  求你了
Nancy, please.
你是我唯一能信任的人
You're the only person I can trust.
有什么违法的事吗
Is something illegal going on?
没有  她只是碰上了点麻烦
No. She's just a girl in trouble
需要找个地方避避
who needs a place to stay.
-我们得小心点  -至少让我先见见她吧
- We have to be discreet. - Can I at least meet her first?
我现在就要答复
I need to know now.
好吧
Okay, I guess.
谢谢
Thank you.
没什么条件  拉里
There's no catch, Larry.
款项落实  你的选区就能拿到两千多万
Your district gets over 20 million if the numbers hold.
其中大多数将用于经济发展
And most of the money is earmarked for economic development,
而非科研
not research.
太棒了  但我不仅需要你的支持
That's great, but I need more than your support.
我需要你跟我连署
I need you to be a sponsor.
好极了  拉里
Fantastic, Larry.
太棒了  我要挂了
Great. I'll put you down.
你也是  再见
You too. Bye.
那就只剩克雷伯恩...和普莱斯是吗
So that just leaves Clayburn... and Price?
詹宁斯仍在观望
With Jennings on the fence.
我认识罗杰  我打给他
And I know Roger. I'll call him.
我这周末会跟进另外两人
And I'll track down these other two over the weekend.
今天真的很棒  彼得
Really good work today, Peter.
你看见我的手提包了吗
Do you know where I put my purse?
在这儿
It's right here.
这些是你折的吗
Did you make those?
抱歉  我不是有意偷看的
I'm sorry. I didn't mean to pry.
这个吗  我最近瞎折腾的
Oh, this? I've been fooling around with it a little bit.
我能看看吗
Can I see?
萨拉在美工课上学折这种鸟
Sarah learned how to make these birds in her art class.
她又教会了凯文  他俩就着迷了
Then she taught it to Kevin, and they got obsessed,
家里到处都是小纸片
and there were little pieces of paper all over the apartment.
拿去给孩子们吧
Do you wanna take them for the kids?
不用了  我不能拿
Oh, no. I can't.
拿去吧  反正我最后也会丢掉
Oh, please. I'll just throw them out eventually.
谢谢  他们一定很喜欢
Thank you. They'll love them.
哪天带你的孩子来我家吧
So you should bring the kids by the house
让我见见他们
sometime so I can meet them.
凯文和弗兰克可以一起打电玩
Kevin and Frank can play the video games.
他告诉你的吗
He told you that?
必须承认  我当时有点惊讶
I was a little surprised, I have to admit.
如果有人知道他每天回家都...
If anybody knew he came home every day to...
-可太丢人了  -还有更可怕的秘密呢
- it's embarrassing. - There's worse secrets to have.
是啊  我想也是
Yeah, there are, I suppose.
我跟克雷伯恩和普莱斯谈过后
I'll call you Monday after I talk
周一会给你打电话
to Clayburn and Price.
好的  太棒了  周末愉快  彼得
Okay, great. Have a good weekend, Peter.
你也是
You too.
我让琳达跟副总统谈过了
I had Linda talk to the Vice President.
-他不会过问的  -太感谢了
- He'll keep his nose out of it. - I appreciate that.
他人挺好的
He's a good man,
但现在正是竞选的敏感时期
but this is a very delicate moment in the campaign.
有人提出质疑...
You start spreading doubts, and...
他就是个讨厌鬼  我们都知道
He's a pain in the ass. We all know it.
没必要拐弯抹角  弗兰克
You don't have to mince words, Frank.
不得不说  先生  副总统还是有道理的
I have to say, sir, the Vice President has a point.
我并不十分赞成罗素
I'm not 100% sold on Russo.
我们真的要选经验这么浅的人吗
Do we really wanna go with someone this untested?
弗兰克
Frank?
我们还在打磨他  先生
We're grooming him, sir.
-你什么时候宣布  -下个月
- When do you announce? - Next month.
-时间不够  -你看中他什么
- That's not enough time. - What do you see in him?
我也好奇  他没什么特别之处
I was wondering the same thing. There's not that much to see.
他是个曾经吸毒  正在戒酒的人
What I see is a recovering alcoholic with a history of drug abuse.
-什么  -你说什么  弗兰克
- What? - Excuse me, Frank?
他已经戒了  戒一年了
But he's clean now. Has been for a year.
这是一个救赎的故事  总统先生
This is a redemption story, Mr. President.
一个重回正轨的聪明的年轻人
This is a bright young man who's put his life back on track.
如今他还想帮宾州重回正轨
Now he wants to help put Pennsylvania back on track.
吸毒  弗兰克
Drugs, Frank?
人们喜欢失败者  琳达
People love an underdog, Linda,
人们喜欢看到浪子回头
and people love someone who stands up after they've fallen.
结合这两点  就是个有力的竞选主题
Combine those two, it's a very powerful narrative.
我们所有的民调都显示这会成功
All of our polling indicates this is gonna work.
你想让我们支持一个有药物滥用史的人
You want us to endorse someone with a history of substance abuse?
我们把故事讲给选民听
Let us get his story out there
然后看他们对此的反应
and watch it connect with the voters.
我只在乎胜利  弗兰克
All I care about is a win, Frank.
我认为罗素是我们的最佳选择
And I believe Russo is our best chance.
这不是听天由命  总统先生
This is not a hail Mary, Mr. President,
-这是缜密思考过的一步棋  -总统先生
- this is a well-thought-out game plan. - Mr. President...
我知道我有时会打破常规
I realize that I sometimes think out of the box,
但我上次这么做的时候
but the last time I did,
我们签署了一份教育法案
we signed an education bill.
好  我们不会反对
All right. We won't stand in your way.
但如果事与愿违  弗兰克
But if it backfires, Frank...
我会全程指导彼得
I'll guide Peter every step along the way.
我们不会让您失望  总统先生
We will not disappoint you, Mr. President.
好
Okay.
谢谢您  先生
Thank you, sir.
琳达
Linda.
我没打算这么快都告诉他
I didn't plan on telling him so much so soon,
但如果我不说  琳达会动摇他
but if I didn't, Linda would've swayed him.
打破疑虑最好的利器
There's no better way to overpower a trickle of doubt
莫过于赤裸裸的事实
than with a flood of naked truth.
所以说教育法案很重要
This is why the education bill was so important.
它在我最需要的时候给了我影响力
It bought me influence precisely when I needed it most.
你酒龄有多少年了
How long have you been drinking?
很多年  从我小的时候就开始了
A long time. Since I was a kid.
你第一次喝酒时几岁
How old were you when you had your first drink?
-9岁  -9岁
- Nine. - Nine years old?
没错  我爸在我9岁生日时给了我瓶啤酒
Yeah. My dad gave me a beer for my ninth birthday.
你开始吸毒是什么时候
When did you first start using drugs?
我不会说太细
I won't go into too many specifics
只能说  我过去曾吸食大麻
other than to say I had a few minor brushes
和可卡因  但次数很少
with marijuana and cocaine in the past but not recently,
近年内没有了
and only a handful of times.
除了大麻和可卡因没有其他毒品吗
No other drugs besides marijuana and cocaine?
没有
No.
都是些什么场合
Under what circumstances?
偶尔的社交聚会  不能再多说了
Occasional social gatherings. That's the most I'll say.
你任公职后吸过毒吗
Ever while you were in public office?
不  从没有过  我主要问题是酗酒
No. Never. My chief problem was alcohol.
你戒酒多长时间了
And you've been sober how long now?
-一年多一点  -你为什么戒酒
- A little over a year. - And what made you want to get sober?
两个原因  我的孩子们
Two things. My children,
我爱他们胜过一切
whom I love more than anything else in the world,
再就是对上帝重拾信念
and my renewed faith in God.
佐伊
Zoe.
卢卡斯
Lucas.
我凑巧在附近  我想
I was just in the neighborhood, and I thought...
不  那是撒谎  我在街角的酒吧
No. That's a lie. I was at the bar around the corner.
那间有
The one with the, uh...
我记起有次
and I remembered that time
我送你下班
that I dropped you off after work.
我记得
I knew it was...
是这个街区
This block.
我按了门铃  然后等着
And I, uh, buzzed, and then I waited...
-你喝多了  -我喝多了
- you're wasted. - I'm pretty wasted.
你想知道个大秘密吗
Do you wanna know a deep, dark secret?
现在我们已经不在一起
Now we don't work together...
工作了
anymore.
卢卡斯
Lucas...
我真是受宠若惊
I'm really flattered.
可是我现在
But I'm just not in a place
心思完全不在这方面上
where I'm even thinking romantically right now.
我很抱歉  我
I'm sorry. I, uh...
好吧
Yeah.
现在停过去吗  先生
You want me to pull up now, sir?
我还有钥匙
I still have my key.
如果你需要什么的话  我在厨房
I'll be in the kitchen if you need anything.
谢谢
Thank you.
我买了酒  但是找不到开瓶器
Hey, I got us wine, but I can't find a corkscrew anywhere.
给我
Give it to me.
我需要笔
I need a pen.
-总统给你的那支行吗  -可以
- The pen the President gave you? - That'll work.
你和斯克斯基小姐谈了吗
Did you talk to Ms. Skorsky?
谈了  她说当时挺动情的
I did. She said it was intense.
我觉得卡莉会请她去头条网工作
I think Carly's gonna offer her a job at Slugline.
-是你推动的  -简宁也有兴趣
- Was that your doing? - Janine expressed interest.
我只是做了个顺水人情
I took the next step.
做的好  让别人欠你人情总是好事
Well done. Always good to be owed favors.
我之前在想  你介意我的年龄吗
I was wondering. Do you ever think about my age?
没有  你介意我的年龄吗
No. Does my age bother you?
你肯定有其他的情人  比我年轻的男人
You must have other lovers... men that are younger than me.
-没有  -我并不介意
- No. - Not that I would mind.
毕竟我已经结婚了
I am married, after all.
我没时间找其他情人
I don't have time for other lovers.
该死
Mm. Shit.
变质了  给我
It's turned. Give me that.
你可以直接踩死它
You could've just stepped on it.
我找过管理员让他找人除虫
I have asked the super to get an exterminator in here,
可他不肯
and he won't do it.
所以我每次看到蟑螂或蜘蛛什么的
So anytime I see a cockroach or a spider, or whatever,
我就抓住它们  然后放到他的门口
I try and trap it, and then I leave it by his door.
你真应该找你父母借点钱
You really ought to get your parents to let you borrow some money.
这样你就不用生活在第三世界了
Then you wouldn't have to live in the third world.
我绝不会拿他们的钱
I would never take money from them.
因为他们没有  还是你不想要
Because they don't have it, or because you don't want it.
我不想要
Because I don't want it.
今天是父亲节
It's father's day, you know.
是吗
It is?
你应该给你父亲打个电话
You should call your father.
我明天再打给他
I'll call him tomorrow.
明天你就是忘记父亲节的女儿
Tomorrow you'll be the daughter that forgot father's day
而不是记得这个日子的乖女儿
instead of the one who remembered.
去吧  给他打电话
Go ahead. Call him.
爸爸  抱歉这么晚打给你
Hey, dad. Sorry it's so late.
因为上次我打给她的时候你不在家
'Cause you weren't home the last time I called her.
我和她永远不会对彼此倾吐太多
There's so little she'll ever reveal to me or I to her.
我猜她父亲知道的更少
I bet her father knows even less.
她讲电话的声音肯定要高半个八度
I'm sure she's speaking half an octave higher.
就像她16岁时那样的声音
Same voice she had when she was 16.
跟他说她找到了新工作
Telling him all about her new job,
十分想他
how much she misses him,
很抱歉没给他寄张贺卡
and sorry she didn't send a card.
告诉他一切  唯独不说真话
Telling him everything but the truth.
就像她不告诉我刚才楼下的那个小伙子
Just like she wouldn't tell me about that young man downstairs.
我这不是给你打电话了吗
I'm calling now, all right?
别让我因为这个难受
Don't make me feel bad about it.
这是最好的结果
It was the best thing that could've happened.
我在那儿不合适
I didn't fit in there.
我听过更难听的话  爸爸
I've been called worse, dad.
保守秘密是有价值的
There's a value in having secrets.
像我  像克莱尔  像佐伊这样的人
Creatures like myself, like Claire, like Zoe...
没有秘密  我们就不是自己
we wouldn't be ourselves without them.
另一方面  彼得・罗素
But Peter Russo, on the other hand...
他被他的秘密所束缚
he's trapped by his secrets.
而我就是在给他一个重获自由的机会
What I'm trying to do is give him the opportunity to set himself free.
我不知道
I don't know.
我还不知道
I don't know yet.
毕竟  我们多少只是
After all, we are nothing more or less
我们选择表现出来的样子
than what we choose to reveal.
我在克莱尔和佐伊面前是不同的人
What I am to Claire is not what I am to Zoe,
就像佐伊在我和她爸爸面前也是不同的人
just as Zoe is not to me what she is to her father.
也许要到感恩节
Probably Thanksgiving.
在那之前我可能都回不去
'Cause I don't think I can make it back before then.
好吧  我尽量
Okay. I'll try.
我说了我尽量
I said I'll try.
圣诞节吗  不行
For Christmas. Uh... no.
没有  我现在没在谈恋爱
No. I'm not seeing anyone right now.
不想谈
I don't feel like it.
因为没兴趣
Because I'm not interested in that.
我会告诉你的  爸爸
I would tell you, dad.
是的
Yeah.
好的
Okay.
别担心我
Don't be worried about me.
我很好
I'm fine.
是的
Yeah.
爸爸  我
Dad, I'm in...
我现在过得很好
I'm in a really great place right now.
我尽量
I'm gonna try.
我尽量回去
I'm gonna try to come, okay?
父亲节快乐
Happy Father's Day.
你不祝我父亲节快乐吗
Aren't you gonna wish me a happy Father's Day?
你又没有孩子
You don't have any children.
是吗
Don't I?
翻译  音司忐忑
翻译  u油
翻译  小蟹
翻译  waterlike
翻译  某豚
翻译  小饭
翻译  天意
翻译  风吹日落
翻译  sakura
时间轴  轴人
后期   饿得慌
顾问   老杜
校对   草草
总监  草草
纸牌屋
第一季  第七集
人人影视倾情奉献